(Sheldon:)Oh, here's another one.
(Sheldon:)I wish that the apple pancake
mix was on the top shelf
because it starts with an "A,"
(Sheldon:)but I don't put it there
(Sheldon:)because I don't want you
breaking one of your little legs
(Sheldon:)when you're supposed
to be making my breakfast.
(Leonard:)Is it my turn to talk
about the compromises I make?
(Sheldon:)I wasn't done, but go ahead.
(Sheldon:)He said, compromising.
(Leonard:)Because of you, I'm not allowed
(Leonard:)to adjust the temperature
in my own home.
(Leonard:)I'm not allowed to whistle.
(Leonard:)I don't wear shoes
that might squeak.
(Sheldon:)Well, you're a physicist,
not a circus clown.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, do you realize I don't
live with the woman I love
(Leonard:)because of you?
(Leonard:)No other reason. Just you.
(Sheldon:)Is that true?
Yes, it's true.
The last time
(Leonard:)I brought it up,
you had an emotional breakdown
(Leonard:)and got on a train and ran away.
(Sheldon:)Well, given my history
on the subject,
it seems a little reckless
to bring it up now.